http://www.livingscriptures.com/privacy-terms-of-use/

Skip to content
Why Living Scriptures?
Browse Library
Get a Sneak Peak!
Menu
Why Living Scriptures?
Browse Library
Get a Sneak Peak!
Close
Living Scriptures Privacy Policy Living Scriptures, Inc. (LSI) strives to treat its customers and prospective customers with honesty and behavior that reflects the high values exemplified in our products. Information Security Living Scriptures maintains its in-house database on a separate, secure system from the system that serves this secure website. Web sales are conducted using the latest security protocols using encrypted data. Once an online order is processed the data are transferred to our internal, secure system. Credit card information is preserved on our internal system only for billing credit cards for subscription customers who choose to receive future shipments billed this way. Information Access and Customer Contact You can access all your personally identifiable information that LSI collects by logging in and clicking the My Account link in the box on the top right-hand side of every page. By purchasing from Living Scriptures you agree to receive periodic communication regarding special offers by our electronic phone system to your phone or cell phone provided from the time from us. This communication may also be by mail, email, or text message. It is LSI’s goal to reach customers periodically by phone with special or exclusive offers, but no more frequently than four times per year. Email offers from Living Scriptures and its affiliates LDSFamilyFun.com and Latter-day Harvest (LDHarvest.com) will arrive periodically. Opting out LSI abides by all Federal Do Not Call List regulations. If you do not wish to receive telephone and/or mail contact from us, please contact Customer Service at 1-800-548-4647. You may opt-out of receiving email offers by un-checking the option when logging in and clicking the My Account link in the box on the top right-hand side of every page. Information Sharing Affiliate companies and websites LSI will share customer contact information with its affiliates LDSFamilyFun.com and Latter-day Harvest (LDHarvest.com) for the purposes of mail- or email-based promotion, not to exceed the contact frequency outlined above, and per the contact permission for which a customer either agrees or opts out. In order to access the discount benefits (25% or more every day on thousands of items) at Latter-day Harvest, LSI Customers will need to log-in and manage their account from that separate website. Furthermore, LSI Customers who wish to receive the free FHE lessons, activities, recipes or other content at LDSFamilyFun should sign up, log in and manage their account at that site. Third parties LSI is selective about third parties with whom it does business. We offer third parties opportunity to reach our customers and internal database by way of advertising in direct mail, email or enclosures within our normal shipment cycles. Occasionally we may conduct phone sales on behalf of a noteworthy party. We infrequently rent or sell our lists, reserving that privilege only for third parties that share a similar mission or purpose, seeking to bring to our customers high quality, values-oriented products or services. Policy Revision and Questions Amendments Living Scriptures’ Privacy Policy is reviewed from time to time. Should there be changes and revisions, new versions will be posted on this website. Please check back periodically for updates. Questions For any questions that may not be explicitly covered in this Privacy Policy, please contact our Customer Service department at 1-800-548-4647.
Follow Us
Facebook
Youtube
Twitter
Living Scriptures BlogWeekly FHE LessonsActivity Books
Why Living Scriptures?FeaturesTestimonialsShop DVDsPurchase Gift CardsRedeem a Gift Card
How to WatchBrowse LibraryPricingSupportContact UsRequest a MovieWatch for free
About Living Scriptures
Questions? Call 800-548-4647
© Copyright 2019 Living Scriptures Inc.   |    Privacy Policy   |   Terms and Conditions
//www.livingscriptures.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/clean-videos.jpg
